New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneous Files, 1908-2000; 5; 33.25 cubic ft.
  - Subseries 2: Agriculture and Lawn, Undated; 5.2
    This subseries consists of materials on pesticide use and alternatives for agriculture, and lawn care / landscaping. The latter includes information relating to individual homeowner lawn care/landscaping, as well as that for institutions, particularly golf courses.
    - 5 Year Food and Nutrition Plan, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - Acetic Acid Based Herbicides [Vinegar / Lemon Juice], 2001-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Opportunities and Markets in Delaware and Otsego Counties, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Policy, New Clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Research and Development Grant Program, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - Agriculture in Rural New York State: Action Agenda, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Agro-Chemical Companies, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - Air/Waste/Soil Quality Reports and Articles, 1989; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Appropriate Technology Transfer for Rural Areas [ATTRA], 1990-1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Appropriate Technology Transfer for Rural Areas [ATTRA] -- Rotational Grazing and No-till Farming, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - ATTRA -- Sustainable Weed Management for Agronomic Crops Information Package, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - Beekeepers, 1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - Black Locust Tree Control -- Pine Bush, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Cabbage Field Pests Research and News Clippings, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - Cabbage Root Maggot Research and News Clippings, 1908-1969 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - Cabbage Root Maggot Research and New Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Cabbage Root Maggot Research and News Clippings, 1980-1985 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Campaign for Sustainable Agriculture, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Canadian Agriculture Action Groups, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - Canadian Organic Farming Articles and Conferences, 1985; 1988-1989 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - Cancerous Pesticides in the News, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - Carcinogenic Pesticides on Food, 1992-1999 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - Center for Sustainable Agriculture at Tierra Organic Farms -- Program Agreement with NYS Attorney General's Office, 1997 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - Census of Agriculture Orange County, NY, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - Center for Agricultural Development and Entrepreneurship Membership Information, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - Change In Pesticide Thought, 1998 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - Chemical Fertilizer Issues, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - The Chemical Free Lawn by Warren Schultz, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - Clinton Pesticide Plan and Bill, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - Cleaner Foods, Cleaner Kitchens Alliance / Cuisine Group, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - Community and Rural Development Institute [CARDI] of Cornell University, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - Community Gardening, 1988-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - Community Supported Agriculture, 1991-1992; 1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Composting at Home, 1997-2001; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - Composting -- Controversies and Miscellaneous, 1997-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - Congress and Pesticides, 1987; 1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)
    - Consortium for Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education [CSARE], 1993-1999 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 38)
    - Consumer Attitudes Toward Pesticides, 1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 39)
    - Conventional Agriculture -- Articles, 1990-2002 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - Corn Gluten -- Based Herbicides, 1997-2002; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 42)
      Pest Management Recommendations for Commercial Production and Maintenance of Trees and Shrubs, 1993.
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension, Food Safety, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 43)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension, Lawn Care without Pesticides, 1987-1995 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 44)
    - "Cornell Recommendations for Pest Control for Commercial Production and Maintenance of Trees and Shrubs", 1984-1985 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 45)
    - Cornell University, Press Releases on Agricultural Issues, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 46)
    - Cornell Turf grass Program, Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 47)
    - Cornell Turf grass Program, General Information, Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 48)
    - Crabgrass and Dandelion Control, 1988-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 49)
    - Crop Choice Sponsorship / Genetically Modified Organisms, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - Dandelion and Mowing Height Study, Photograph and Slides, Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - Delaney Clause, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - Delaney Clause and "Negligible Risk", 1988-1990 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Delaney Clause Information -- NYCAP/NCPPR, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - Drift of Pesticides, 1990-2002 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - Economic Impacts of Reduced Pesticide use on Fruits and Vegetables, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Educating Children on Eating Healthy, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - Enviro Health Inspection Service -- Organic Lawn Care and Gardening, 1997 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Farm Bill 1985, 1984-1990 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Farm Bill 1990, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - Farm Bills 1995, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - Farm Bill 2002 -- Policy Initiatives, 2001 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - Farm Marketing, 1988; 1994 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Farm Research, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - The Farm Worker, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - Farm Worker Advocacy Day, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Farm Worker Justice Fund, 1989; 1991 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Farm Worker Outreach Programs, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Farm Worker Safety, 1985-2001; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20-21)
    - Farm Workers in NYS, 1996; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - Farm Workers, Labor Issues, 1991-1997 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - Farm Workers Legal Services in New York, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - Farm Workers -- Pesticide Exposure, 1994; 1996-1997; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - Fear in the Fields -- Seattle Times News Clipping, 1997 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - Fish and Wild life, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - Flame Weeding, 1992-2002 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - FLO Agricultural Project Notebook, 1986 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - Flowers and Pesticides, 2001 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - Flowers and Work Production, 1999; 2002 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - Food Co-op Conference, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - Food Co-ops, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - Food -- Pesticide and Chemical Residues, 1994-2002 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Food Quality Protection Act, 2001 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - Food Residue Testing -- Correspondence, Reports, and Notes, 1986-1990 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - Food Safety Articles, 1988-1994; Undated (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37-39)
    - Food Safety -- New York State Legislation and Tracy Frisch / NYCAP Involvement, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - Frisch [Tracey], Sustainable Agriculture, New York State Legislation, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)
    - Gardening, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 42)
    - Gardening, IPM 1990, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 43)
    - Genetic Engineering / Biotechnology, 1996-2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1-3)
    - Genetically Engineered Food, 1988-2000; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Genetically Modified Organisms -- General Information, 2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - Genetically Modified Organisms -- New York Times Article re: Trader Joe's ban on GMO, 2001 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - Genetically Modified Organisms -- New Release, 2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - GMO Lobby Day, 2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - Gold / Another Way to Be Green Project, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Golf -- Aquatic Impacts, 1990-1997; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Golf -- Audubon Cooperative Sanctuary Program, 1995-2001 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - Gold -- Contacts, 1991-1997 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - Gold and Pesticides -- New York State Attorney General, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - Gold Course Pesticides -- Adirondack Park Agency, 1992; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Gold Courses -- Environmental Issues, 1993-2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - Gold Courses -- Information Collected by Vilma Gregoropoulous, 1993-1999 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - Gold Courses [Information Packet], 1990-1997 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Golf Environmental Principles, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Golf -- Human Health Issues, 1991-1996 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Golf -- "IPM on Gold Courses", 1997 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - Golf -- NCAP / Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - Golf -- Organic, 1995-2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22)
    - Golf -- Proposed Courses, 1996-2001 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 23)
    - Golf -- Southwestern U.S. / Desert, 1989-1993 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - Golf / Turf grass Management -- Community Used Chemicals, 1999-2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - Golf -- Water Quality Enhancement, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - Gold -- Woodcrest Country Club Pesticide Use, 1998 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - Grassroots Calgary / Grassroots N.W. Environmental Awareness Society, Lawns for Kids, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - Great Lakes: Great Gardening Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - Greater New York Natural Organic Landscapes Network Member Advertising, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - Greater New York Natural Organic Landscapes Network Member Listing and Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - Greater New York Natural Organic Landscapes Network Registration Forms, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - Hazardous Waste in Fertilizers, 1997-2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - Hot Water, Steam and Infrared Weeding Techniques, 1992-2001 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Houseplants, Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - Hydroponics, Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - Imported Food, 1987-1989; 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)
    - "In Our Own Backyard", Pesticide Use in NYS, 1987 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 38)
    - Insects and Diseases of Trees and Forests, Articles, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 39)
    - Integrated Pest Management Programs in Landscaping, 1985-1988; 1992 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 40)
    - International Food Safety, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 41)
    - International Sustainable Agriculture Groups and Programs, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 42)
    - IPM for Golf Courses, 1997-2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 43)
    - IPM for Trees and Shrubs on School Grounds, ca. 1996 or later (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 44)
    - IPM in National Parks, 1991-1994; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 45)
    - IPM / New York State Office of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation, 1988-1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 46)
    - IPM Program at North Shore Country Club, Glenview, IL, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 47)
    - Landscape Pest Control Strategies and New Clippings, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 48)
    - Landscape Pests and Damages News Clippings, 1984-1989; 1991 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 49)
    - Landscaping and Lawn care Referrals, 1999-2002; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 50)
    - Landscaping -- Ecological/Organic, 1990-1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 51)
    - Landscaping, Handwritten Notes, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 52)
    - Lawn -- Alternative Vegetation, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 53)
    - Lawn -- Biological Urban Gardening Services [BUGS], 1989-1994 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 54)
    - Lawn Care Alternatives / Natural Lawn Care, 1986-2002 (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 55)
    - Lawn Care and Water Resources News Clippings, 1993; Undated (Box 3 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 56)
    - Lawn Care Certification, 1996-1998 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 1)
    - Lawn Care -- Contracting For, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 2)
    - Lawn Care Information, 1990-2002 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 3)
    - Lawn Care Pesticide Issues, 1990-2002 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 4)
    - Lawn Care Pesticides: A Guide For Action, Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 5)
    - Lawn Care Without Pesticides, Strategies and News Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 6)
    - Lawn Chemicals and Pesticide Dangers, News Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 7)
    - Lawn -- Citizen Activism, 1986-1991; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 8)
    - Lawn -- Dandelions, 1990-2002 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 9)
    - Lawn -- Disease Control, 1985-2001 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 10)
    - Lawn -- Ecological Supplies, 1990-1993; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 11)
    - Lawn -- Fertilizers, 1992-1998; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 12)
    - Lawn -- Insect Control, 1984-1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 13)
    - Lawn -- IPM -- EPA, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 14)
    - Lawn / Landscaping -- Miscellaneous, 1986-1997 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 15)
    - Lawn Letter [to editor] -- Response to Inquiry, 1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 16)
    - Lawn -- Mowing, 1991-1994; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 17)
    - Lawn -- Natural / Organic, 1988-1995 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 18)
    - Lawn -- Natural Organic Standards, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 19)
    - Lawn Packet -- NYCAP, 1989-1992 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 20)
    - Lawn -- Pesticide Campaign 1994 -- Capital District, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 21)
    - Lawn Pesticides, 1986-1995 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 22-23)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Activist Flyers, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 24)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Advertising, 1988-1993 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 25)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Albany Press, 1987-1993 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 26)
    - Lawn Pesticides: An Unacceptable Risk, 2002 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 27)
    - Lawn Pesticides and Pest Management: A NYCAP Information Packet, 1990 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 28)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Bird Deaths, 1980-1990 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 29)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Buffalo Press, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 30)
    - Lawn Pesticides -- Campaign Sample Materials, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 31)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Canada, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 32)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- ChemLawn, 1987-1991; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 33)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Connecticut, 1989-1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 34)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Consumer Protection, 1989-1994 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 35)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides / David Blumkin, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 36)
    - Lawn -- Pesticides -- Hazards, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 4 (5-Programs, Distributed Information and Miscellaneou), Folder 37)